<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Time Machine For Peace.</title>
    <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Time Machine For Peace.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Daily Log: 06/18/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061821/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061821/</guid>
      <description>TODO: . REview conversation chain (1130) . jump on kickstarter to get in thinking zone . create dedicated space on tmfp.wp.computer for drafting kickstarter . post credentials on bmakusa.wp.computer (0617) . need to partition posts into separate log spaces, etc . create FAQ and write/begin populating . MIGRATE BMAKUSA.WP.COMPUTER TM CONTENT TO TMFP.WP.COMPUTER 
 &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
[0500.061821]
Market day, hygeine, brain-boot, setup booth.
&amp;ndash;new booth layout. I want to give visitors more space today and see if the new &amp;lsquo;talk to me&amp;rsquo; bell works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Notes: 06/18/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/market/marketnotes061821/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/market/marketnotes061821/</guid>
      <description>New bell installed. Ring for choose-your-own-adventure.
Brian / Maya, if you are reading this, you should stop by the booth for a picture with your UPC support tokens and I. It would help with the Kickstarter I am angling toward.
LOL&amp;hellip;Bill couple tents down asked me if I was Bahai Faith.
Visitor interaction log (conversation chain):
(1130) Dylan from highschool! Teal paperclip. CYOA worked pretty well&amp;hellip;started with hi, interest in rocks&amp;hellip;explained 1-bit rock computer, on to extracting tech value and apply to productivity systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Notes: 06/19/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/market/marketnotes061921/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/market/marketnotes061921/</guid>
      <description>Saturday
Visitor interaction log (conversation chain):
(1000) Brandon &amp;amp; Tristan, copper + green
High and low level discussion about project, how individuals can jump in and apply the idea of universal peace to their lives&amp;hellip;on world peace computers as systems that people naturally employ in their worlds&amp;hellip;on incentivization of peace as a process&amp;hellip;
(1150) Gail, blue, peace music idea i (1230) Reynolds, red, airforce,
(1310) Andy, green, explaining peace as an individualistic improvement process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Log: 06/17/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061721/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061721/</guid>
      <description>TODO: . REview conversation chain (1130) . jump on kickstarter to get in thinking zone . create dedicated space on tmfp.wp.computer for drafting kickstarter . post credentials on bmakusa.wp.computer . need to partition posts into separate log spaces, etc . create FAQ and write/begin populating . MIGRATE BMAKUSA.WP.COMPUTER TM CONTENT TO TMFP.WP.COMPUTER 
 &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
[0900.061721]
Creating FAQ section, to introduce a more conversational element to the the broadcast communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Log: 06/16/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061621/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061621/</guid>
      <description>TODO: . REview conversation chain (1130) . JUmp on kickstarter to get in thinking zone . create dedicated space on tmfp.wp.computer for drafting kickstarter . post credentials on bmakusa.wp.computer . need to partition posts into separate log spaces, etc 
 &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
[1100.061621]
Quick color review for conversation chain.
Need to start using online space in place of physical notebooks, at least for main working notes.
(1130)
need to create market recaps later</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Log: 06/15/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061521/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061521/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;&amp;lt;
[2100.061521]
Peace consulting work for storage landlord.
Excercise for health and processing, mountain: high intensity intervals, active rest with pushups/situps. Total pushups, 170; total situps, 300ish; pullup set stretch sandwich warmdown, total pullups, 70.
Excercise process thoughts (incomplete conversation review), re kickstarter:  Use website population as writing blocks for campaign. (Patrick) Not “A” movement. My contrarian perspective: Every Human has a unique contrarian perspective, which via clever technologies and translation techniques, may all be aligned as one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Log: 06/14/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061421/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/daily/dailylog061421/</guid>
      <description>&amp;amp;[2300.061421&amp;amp;]
Long day, but solved a bunch of head problems and made enough money to afford hike/exercise gas for summer.
Finished day with non-verbal broadcast communication piece.
Nonverbal communication broadcast, mindmapping/reflection piece, 06/14/21.
 I am exhausted though.
Three 10hr sleeps scheduled before next market weekend. I will have ~ 32 hours (after deducting excercise/hygeine time) for kickstarter production.
-Blair
[2300.061421]
~
[0600.061421]
Market weekend was super fulfilling, but intense and a lot to process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Recap: 06/13/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/booth/marketrecap061321/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/booth/marketrecap061321/</guid>
      <description>~ to update after process day {06/14} riding four wheelers for gas cash ~
-Blair</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Recap: 06/12/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/booth/marketrecap061221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/booth/marketrecap061221/</guid>
      <description>Daily market recap:
Too tired (and too busy setting up proper blog at moment) to write much. Attached picture: conversation chain of the day. Each link represents a (highly) significant conversation about peace. Community peace art. And after reflecting on the wisdom I gleaned from all the wise people who spoke with me, a thought from me to you: Without courage, you have nothing. I think you need to devote your life to something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Recap: 06/11/21</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/booth/marketrecap061121/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/booth/marketrecap061121/</guid>
      <description>Fridays at the market are slow, great for taking things methodically, and really soaking it all in. The configuration today was slightly different than last Sunday. I repeated the front table for greeting ease, repeated the interior table, this time with conceptual text pieces that I am annotating throughout the day. I also reintroduced the briefcase cluster computer along the back, and this time included a library of curious influences for casual perusing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Time Machine For Peace (a social invention project)</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a site to chronicle (and eventually coordinate) the Time Machine For Peace social invention project.
Please visit Github to view site change history.
My target update frequency is daily.
This is a diagram expressing topological gestalt. Definition of symbols are below written piece.
 A NOTE ON PERSONAL STYLE:
 I operate on a different frequency. I am the producer right now. Until that changes for this project, expect constant changes everywhere, but consistently inconsistently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IN</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/in/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/in/</guid>
      <description>TRO  Welcome. This is market research. I am technically an electrical engineer. Electrical engineers think largely in terms of **filters**. We use filters in electronics to separate signals. The way I present this project makes heavy use of filters. I need to identify my target audience for Phase 1. These are people who get it. These are people who want it. These are people who need it. If you find yourself reading past this page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>06/16/21 - Garbage 1</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/garbage1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/garbage1/</guid>
      <description>00 - Kickstarter Pretext
 piece reflections / review / self-comments
(061721) This feels **way** too dramatic..lots of outside voice shouting My mood while writing was definitely leaning toward the red (emotional) side {TODO . highlight these dramatic portions in red} {TODO . dedramatize / take out the shouting} ! The dump was good though...got me thinking about FAQ ! Also got me thinking about treating tmfp.wp.computer as exhibit ! (traverse via section menu, left to right) Taking about the bit about my dad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>06/20/21 - Project Description</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/campaignprofile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/campaignprofile/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Blair. I&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce myself:
I&amp;rsquo;m approaching the Kickstarter community because I am looking for help getting on my feet, and I want to establish a lasting relationship within the communities that I am most interested in working with. To prepare for this kickstarter, I set up a market research and development booth for the summer at my local weekend market up here in Anchorage, Alaska, where I call home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>06/23/21 - Project Description V2</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/campaignprofilev2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/campaignprofilev2/</guid>
      <description>This is a planet-benefit project.
 Current pretext note, 062321:
Instead of attempting to describe this big idea in a pretty package, this Kickstarter and the paper trail that represents my efforts, will serve as an imperfect example of universal peace. Instead of attempting to just tell you, I will do my best to show you. This campaign will probably change dramatically over the course of the next two months. Hopefully after meeting the funding goal, by a year&amp;rsquo;s end following the conclusion of this campaign, I will have a pretty packaged current edition of the big idea to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>07/04/21 - Written Project Description</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/projectdescription0704/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/projectdescription0704/</guid>
      <description>These are screen grabs from the Kickstarter project description before a total overhaul on 072321.
                </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>07/23/21 - Project description video practice and process</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/projectdescriptionvideopractice0715/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/projectdescriptionvideopractice0715/</guid>
      <description>These are videos of me practicing and figuring out how to make a Kickstarter project description video and structure content in a way that is true to my style, etc. I absolutely hate watching myself, but it must be done. I don&amp;rsquo;t have time right now to annotate all the self-criticisms and changes made since then, so I won&amp;rsquo;t. I recommend saving yourself time by watching on 2x speed.
To simplify things, the card computer is no longer a reward for supporting the kickstarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>08/07/21 - Written Project Description</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/projectdescription0807/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/projectdescription0807/</guid>
      <description>These are screen grabs from the Kickstarter project description before a total overhaul on 080721.
                              </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>_FAQ Overview</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/overview/</guid>
      <description>Ok. After doing some timespace travel to review my past experience, I determined that I need to avoid some past communication mistakes. Instead of feeling like I need to linearize my headspace all at once for some invisible imaginary general audience in my head, I will instead approach content delivery as an interactive choose-your-own-adventure.
This section will be the most important section within the timemachineforpeace subdomain space.
The FAQ section is a collection of answers to common questions that people close to me have asked over the years, and answers to common questions that people from the Anchorage Market booth have asked over the course of the summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blair&#39;s (blairmunroakusa) credentials</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/context/bmakusacred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/context/bmakusacred/</guid>
      <description> CONTEXT NOTES BELOW
   CONTEXT NOTES BELOW
   CONTEXT NOTES BELOW
   CONTEXT NOTES BELOW
   CONTEXT NOTES BELOW
   CONTEXT NOTES BELOW
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blair&#39;s (blairmunroakusa) Library</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/context/bmakusalib/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/context/bmakusalib/</guid>
      <description>This library is incomplete. If I had the money, this would be about 300% larger. I like physical copies of things, so all my electronic stuff would be here also.
Of the works in my library, I have seriously studied about 25% of these pieces. 45% I have read once. 25% I have reviewed and use as inspiration for my work. 5% I have not read, but the book serves as a future pointer, or a placeholder for future reading/work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dedication</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/dedication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/dedication/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a long list, but I could easily make it much much longer.
I dedicate the Time Machine For Peace social invention project to the following people:  Victims of war in all forms, both external and internal American veterans who took the oath to support and defend the values of the US Constitution &amp;hellip;especially those who paid the ultimate price &amp;hellip;especially those who embrace a fierce hatred for war. Without you, I would not have the immense priviledge up upbringing in domestic peace that allowed me to grow into what I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logs</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/logs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/logs/logs/</guid>
      <description>BACK
PRELUDE I&amp;rsquo;m Blair.
I need help. First, I need to fund my efforts, so that I can devote my undivided attention to seeing this project through.
I have been
BACK</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Universal Peace</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/concepts/universalpeace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/concepts/universalpeace/</guid>
      <description>This is where I will transparently work on the Kickstarter campaign to fund our efforts (right now funding to afford salary for me and the mouse in my pocket).
PRELUDE I&amp;rsquo;m Blair.
I need help. First, I need to fund my efforts, so that I can devote my undivided attention to seeing this project through.
I have been
OVERVIEW </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why?</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/why/</guid>
      <description>This is a very deep and common question. I will dump common variants for now, hardest to easiest, organize later. Why, Blair? 00, because ~ Well, why not. I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s because I can. To me sparking off Universal Peace seems like something worth trying. 
01, compulsion ~ Truthfully though, this is a primal compulsion. I cannot escape this drive inside me. I have tried to change this aspect of my being with medicine, drugs, alcohol, escapism, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>~ MORE ABOUT-ME</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/moreaboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/moreaboutme/</guid>
      <description>My mission is to help accelerate the advent of world peace, by initializing a peace process called Universal Peace. By my economic thesis, world peace is going to happen, and its advent is only a matter of time.
So I&amp;rsquo;ve been inventing a time machine for peace (a general purpose stuff computer, called a world piece computer) to serve as a world peace accelerator. This is my lifework, and I have been motivated in this direction for as long as I can remember.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>~ MORE ABOUT-ME</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/notsonutshell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/kickstarter/notsonutshell/</guid>
      <description>My mission is to help accelerate the advent of world peace, by initializing a peace process called Universal Peace. By my economic thesis, world peace is going to happen, and its advent is only a matter of time.
So I&amp;rsquo;ve been inventing a time machine for peace (a general purpose stuff computer, called a world piece computer) to serve as a world peace accelerator. This is my lifework, and I have been motivated in this direction for as long as I can remember.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
