<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FAQs on Time Machine For Peace.</title>
    <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FAQs on Time Machine For Peace.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>_FAQ Overview</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/overview/</guid>
      <description>Ok. After doing some timespace travel to review my past experience, I determined that I need to avoid some past communication mistakes. Instead of feeling like I need to linearize my headspace all at once for some invisible imaginary general audience in my head, I will instead approach content delivery as an interactive choose-your-own-adventure.
This section will be the most important section within the timemachineforpeace subdomain space.
The FAQ section is a collection of answers to common questions that people close to me have asked over the years, and answers to common questions that people from the Anchorage Market booth have asked over the course of the summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why?</title>
      <link>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timemachineforpeace.wp.computer/faq/why/</guid>
      <description>This is a very deep and common question. I will dump common variants for now, hardest to easiest, organize later. Why, Blair? 00, because ~ Well, why not. I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s because I can. To me sparking off Universal Peace seems like something worth trying. 
01, compulsion ~ Truthfully though, this is a primal compulsion. I cannot escape this drive inside me. I have tried to change this aspect of my being with medicine, drugs, alcohol, escapism, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
